<resources>
    <string name="app_name">management-app</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="gender_array">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- School items -->
    <string-array name="school_array">
        <item>PHINMA URDANETACITY</item>
        <item>UPANG DAGUPAN</item>
        <item>MISYUBIBI</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="details"><u>Click hereto see details.</u></string>

    <string name="aerial_view"><b>AERIAL VIEW</b></string>
    <string name="street_view"><b>STREET VIEW</b></string>

    <string name="flex_learning"><b><big>FLEX LEARNING</big></b>
        \n <li>Both Distance Learning + Face-to-Face Sessions</li>
        \n <li>Teacher support will be provided via calls, texts, or social media</li>
        \n <li>6-8 subjects in 1 semester</li>
    </string>

    <string name="rad_learning"><b><big>RAD LEARNING</big></b>
        \n <li>Largely Home-based with virtual coaching</li>
        \n <li>For students who cannot come to school</li>
        \n <li>Suited for working students who need flexible learning setup</li>
        \n <li>2 subjects in 1 moth</li>
    </string>


























    
    <string name="rad_learning_description">RAD<b> (Reinforced Adaptive Development) </b>Learning at <b>PHINMA University of Pangasinan </b>(UPANG) is an innovative approach to education designed to adapt to the unique needs and circumstances of each student. This system combines traditional classroom learning with advanced technological tools and methodologies to create a flexible, student-centered educational experience.
    \n \n <li> <b>Blended Learning:</b> RAD integrates face-to-face instruction with online learning, offering students the flexibility to access course materials, participate in discussions, and complete assignments at their own pace.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Personalized Learning Paths:</b> Each students learning journey is tailored to their individual strengths, weaknesses, and learning styles. Adaptive learning technologies analyze student performance and provide customized feedback and resources.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Continuous Assessment:</b> RAD emphasizes ongoing assessment rather than traditional high-stakes exams. This allows for regular feedback and adjustments to the learning process, ensuring students stay on track and master the material.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Collaborative Environment:</b> Students engage in group projects and peer-to-peer learning, fostering a collaborative and supportive community. This approach helps develop critical soft skills such as teamwork, communication, and problem-solving.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Industry-Linked Curriculum:</b> The curriculum is designed in collaboration with industry partners to ensure that it meets the current demands of the job market. This ensures that graduates are job-ready and possess the skills that employers are looking for.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Support Systems:</b> RAD Learning provides comprehensive support through academic advising, tutoring, and mental health services. This holistic approach ensures that students have the resources they need to succeed both academically and personally.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Integration:</b> The use of cutting-edge educational technologies, including learning management systems, virtual labs, and interactive multimedia content, enhances the learning experience and keeps students engaged.</li></string>

    <string name="flex_learning_description">FLEX<b> (Flexible Learning Experience) </b>at <b>PHINMA University of Pangasinan (UPANG) </b>is an educational model designed to provide students with a versatile and adaptive learning environment that caters to their individual needs and lifestyles. This approach combines various learning modalities to ensure that education is accessible, engaging, and effective for all students.
    \n \n <li> <b>Hybrid Learning:</b> FLEX incorporates a blend of traditional classroom instruction and online learning. This hybrid model allows students to participate in both in-person and virtual classes, offering the flexibility to balance their studies with other commitments.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Self-Paced Learning:</b> Students have the option to progress through course materials at their own pace. This self-directed approach empowers learners to take control of their education, advancing quickly through familiar topics while spending more time on challenging concepts.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Interactive Online Platforms:</b> FLEX utilizes advanced learning management systems (LMS) and interactive online platforms that provide access to lectures, assignments, quizzes, and discussion forums. These tools enhance the learning experience by making it more interactive and engaging.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Customized Learning Paths:</b> Each student's learning journey is tailored to their individual needs and goals. Adaptive learning technologies analyze student performance and preferences, providing personalized recommendations and resources to support their academic growth.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Collaborative Projects:</b> Students participate in collaborative projects and group activities, fostering a sense of community and enhancing teamwork skills. These projects often involve real-world applications, preparing students for professional environments.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Accessibility and Inclusivity:</b> FLEX is designed to be accessible to all students, regardless of their location or circumstances. Online resources and flexible scheduling options ensure that education is available to those who may face geographical, financial, or time constraints.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Comprehensive Support:</b> FLEX Learning offers a range of support services, including academic advising, tutoring, and counseling. These resources help students navigate their educational journey, overcome challenges, and achieve their goals.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Industry-Relevant Curriculum:</b> The curriculum is developed in collaboration with industry experts to ensure that it is relevant to current job market demands. This focus on practical, real-world skills helps students become job-ready upon graduation.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Continuous Assessment and Feedback:</b> FLEX emphasizes continuous assessment through regular quizzes, assignments, and feedback. This approach allows students to monitor their progress and make necessary adjustments to their learning strategies.</li></string>

    <string name="facetoface_learning_description"><b>Face-to-Face</b> learning at <b>PHINMA University of Pangasinan</b> (UPANG) is the traditional, in-person approach to education, where students and instructors interact directly within the classroom environment. This method emphasizes personal engagement, immediate feedback, and a structured learning experience, fostering a vibrant academic community.
    \n \n <li> <b>Direct Interaction:</b> Students benefit from real-time, face-to-face interactions with instructors and peers. This direct engagement facilitates immediate clarification of doubts, dynamic discussions, and personalized feedback.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Structured Environment:</b> The physical classroom provides a structured setting that supports discipline and focus. Scheduled classes and a fixed timetable help students manage their time effectively and maintain a consistent study routine.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Hands-On Learning:</b> Face-to-Face learning at PHINMA UPANG emphasizes experiential learning through lab sessions, workshops, and practical exercises. This hands-on approach is particularly beneficial for courses requiring physical demonstration and practice.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Community Building:</b> In-person classes foster a sense of community and camaraderie among students. Social interactions, group projects, and extracurricular activities build strong relationships and enhance collaborative skills.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Immediate Feedback:</b> Instructors can provide instant feedback and support during class. This immediate response helps students correct mistakes, understand concepts better, and stay engaged with the material.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Enhanced Communication Skills:</b> Face-to-Face learning develops essential communication skills. Students practice public speaking, active listening, and interpersonal communication, which are crucial for personal and professional success.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Resource Accessibility:</b> On-campus resources, including libraries, labs, and study spaces, are readily available to students. Access to these facilities supports research, experimentation, and group study sessions.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Extracurricular Opportunities:</b> Students can participate in various on-campus activities, clubs, and organizations. These opportunities enrich the university experience, promoting personal growth and leadership development.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Cultural and Social Exposure:</b> In-person learning exposes students to diverse perspectives and cultures through direct interaction with classmates and faculty. This exposure broadens their understanding and appreciation of different viewpoints.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Health and Safety Measures:</b> PHINMA UPANG ensures a safe learning environment by implementing health and safety protocols. These measures include regular sanitation, social distancing, and health monitoring to protect the well-being of students and staff.</li></string>

    <string name="hka_description"><b>The 25% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b> is a financial aid program designed to assist deserving students in pursuing higher education. This scholarship aims to alleviate the financial burden on students and their families by providing a 25% reduction in tuition fees. PHINMA UPANG is committed to making quality education accessible to more students, and the HK Scholarship is one of the initiatives to support this mission.
    \n \n <li> <b>Reduced Financial Burden:</b> With a 25% discount on tuition fees, the scholarship significantly reduces the overall cost of education, making it more affordable for students and their families.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Access to Quality Education:</b> The scholarship enables more students to access the high-quality education and facilities offered by PHINMA UPANG, which can enhance their learning experience and future career prospects.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Encouragement of Academic Excellence:</b> By providing financial assistance, the scholarship encourages students to strive for academic excellence without the constant worry of financial constraints.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Increased Opportunities:</b> The reduction in tuition fees allows students to allocate their resources to other educational needs such as books, transportation, and living expenses, thereby providing a more comprehensive educational experience.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Support for Deserving Students:</b> The HK Scholarship is designed to support students who demonstrate academic potential and financial need, ensuring that deserving students are given the opportunity to succeed.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Community Building:</b> Scholarships like the HK Scholarship foster a sense of community and support within the university, as students who receive financial aid are often more engaged and motivated to give back to their peers and the institution.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Long-Term Benefits:</b> By investing in the education of students, PHINMA UPANG is contributing to the development of skilled professionals who can positively impact their communities and the country’s future.</li></string>

    <string name="hkb_description"><b>The 50% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b> is a generous financial aid program designed to support academically promising and financially needy students. This scholarship provides a 50% reduction in tuition fees, significantly easing the financial burden on students and their families. PHINMA UPANG, committed to making quality education accessible to more students, offers the HK Scholarship to help deserving individuals achieve their academic and career aspirations.
    \n \n <li> <b>Substantial Financial Relief:</b> By offering a 50% discount on tuition fees, the scholarship substantially reduces the cost of education, making it more affordable for students and their families.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Enhanced Access to Quality Education:</b> The scholarship allows more students to access the high-quality education, resources, and facilities provided by PHINMA UPANG, improving their overall academic experience and future prospects.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Promotion of Academic Excellence:</b> Financial support through the HK Scholarship motivates students to maintain high academic standards, fostering a culture of excellence and perseverance.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Broader Educational Opportunities:</b> The reduced financial burden enables students to allocate funds to other essential needs such as textbooks, transportation, and living expenses, enhancing their educational journey.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Support for Deserving Students:</b> The HK Scholarship specifically targets students who exhibit academic potential and financial need, ensuring that those who deserve support receive it.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Community and Peer Support:</b> Recipients of the scholarship often become more engaged in campus activities, contributing to a supportive and vibrant university community.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Long-Term Impact:</b> By investing in students' education, PHINMA UPANG helps develop skilled professionals who can positively impact their communities and contribute to national development.</li>
    \n \n <li> <b>Reduction of Financial Stress:</b> With half of the tuition fee covered, students can focus more on their
    studies and personal development, without the constant worry of financial challenges.</li></string>

    <string name="hkc_description"><b>The 75% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b> is an exceptional financial aid program aimed at supporting highly deserving students with significant financial needs. This scholarship offers a 75% reduction in tuition fees, greatly alleviating the financial burden on students and their families. PHINMA UPANG is dedicated to providing accessible quality education, and the HK Scholarship is a key initiative to ensure that more students can achieve their academic goals.
        \n <li> <b>Significant Financial Assistance:</b> The 75% discount on tuition fees substantially lowers the cost of education, making it significantly more affordable for students and their families.</li>
        \n <li> <b>Access to Superior Education:</b> The scholarship ensures that students have access to the high-quality education, resources, and facilities provided by PHINMA UPANG, enhancing their learning experience and future opportunities.</li>
        \n <li> <b>Encouragement of High Academic Standards:</b> Financial support through the HK Scholarship encourages students to maintain excellent academic performance, fostering a culture of dedication and achievement.</li>
        \n <li> <b>Comprehensive Educational Opportunities:</b> The significant reduction in financial burden allows students to allocate resources to other essential needs such as books, transportation, and living expenses, enriching their overall educational journey.</li>
        \n <li> <b>Focus on Deserving Students:</b> The HK Scholarship is designed to support students who demonstrate outstanding academic potential and substantial financial need, ensuring that those who need it most receive support.</li>
        \n <li> <b>Enhanced Campus Involvement:</b> Scholarship recipients often become more active in campus activities and organizations, contributing to a dynamic and supportive university community.</li>
        \n <li> <b>Long-Term Community Impact:</b> By investing in the education of students, PHINMA UPANG helps develop skilled professionals who can make meaningful contributions to their communities and the nation's progress.</li>
        \n <li> <b>Reduction of Financial Stress:</b> With a significant portion of tuition fees covered, students can concentrate more on their studies and personal growth without the constant worry of financial challenges.</li>
    <li> <b>Encouragement of Social Mobility:</b> The scholarship plays a vital role in promoting social mobility by enabling students from lower-income backgrounds to access higher education and improve their socio-economic status.</li></string>

    <string name="hkd_description"><b>The 100% Hawak Kamay (HK) Student Assistant (SA) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b> is a prestigious financial aid program designed for academically talented and financially disadvantaged students. This scholarship offers a full 100% reduction in tuition fees in exchange for students participating in a student assistantship program. By combining financial aid with practical work experience, the HK SA Scholarship aims to develop well-rounded individuals prepared for both academic and professional success.
        \n \n <li> name="hkd1"><b>Benefits of the 100% Hawak Kaway (HK) Student Assistant (SA) Scholarship</b></li>>
        \n \n <li><b>Complete Financial Coverage:</b> The scholarship covers 100% of tuition fees, completely eliminating the financial burden of education and making it accessible for students from all financial backgrounds.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Work Experience and Skill Development:</b> As part of the student assistantship program, students gain valuable work experience, developing essential skills such as time management, teamwork, and problem-solving.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Access to Quality Education:</b> The scholarship allows recipients to benefit from the high-quality education, resources, and facilities provided by PHINMA UPANG, enhancing their learning experience and future career opportunities.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Encouragement of Academic Excellence:</b> With full financial support, students are motivated to maintain high academic standards and focus on their studies without the distraction of financial concerns.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Holistic Development:</b> The combination of academic and practical work experience fosters the holistic development of students, preparing them for the challenges of the professional world.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Support for Deserving Students:</b> The HK SA Scholarship targets students who demonstrate academic potential and financial need, ensuring that those who are most deserving receive the support they need to succeed.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Community and Peer Engagement:</b> Scholarship recipients often become more involved in campus activities and contribute to a supportive and vibrant university community.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Long-Term Career Benefits:</b> The work experience gained through the student assistantship program enhances students resumes, making them more competitive in the job market and better prepared for their chosen careers.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Reduction of Financial Stress:</b> With the full tuition fee covered, students can focus more on their studies and personal growth rather than worrying about financial constraints.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Empowerment and Confidence:</b> Receiving a full scholarship boosts students confidence and self-esteem, empowering them to pursue their goals with greater determination and resilience.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>Networking Opportunities:</b> Working as a student assistant provides opportunities to build professional networks within the university, which can be beneficial for future career prospects.</li>>
        \n \n <li> <b>The 100% Hawak Kamay (HK) Student Assistant (SA) Scholarship is an integral part of PHINMA UPANG’s commitment to providing accessible, affordable, and high-quality education. This scholarship not only alleviates financial burdens but also equips students with practical skills and experiences, empowering them to achieve their full potential and make meaningful contributions to society.</b></li>>
    </string>

    <string name="aboutus_description">
    <b>About PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b>
   \n \n <li>PHINMA UPANG, located in Dagupan City, Pangasinan, Philippines, is part of the PHINMA Education network. It provides quality education that transforms lives and communities, offering various undergraduate and graduate programs.</li>
    \n \n<li><b>Mission and Vision:</b> PHINMA UPANG aims to provide accessible, affordable education and envisions itself as a leader in innovative and transformative education, producing academically competent, socially responsible, and globally competitive graduates.</li>
   \n \n <li><b>Academic Excellence:</b> The university offers programs in Business, Engineering, IT, Education, Health Sciences, and Arts and Sciences, using a learner-centered approach that integrates theory with practical application.</li>
    \n \n<li><b>Facilities and Resources:</b> PHINMA UPANG features state-of-the-art facilities, including modern classrooms, laboratories, a comprehensive library, and specialized research centers, fostering a conducive learning environment.</li>
    \n \n<li><b>Community Engagement:</b> The university emphasizes community engagement and social responsibility through outreach programs and local partnerships, encouraging student participation to develop civic duty and social awareness.</li>
    \n \n<li><b>Student Life:</b> PHINMA UPANG offers vibrant student life with various extracurricular activities, promoting teamwork, leadership, and holistic development.</li>
    \n \n<li><b>Support Services:</b> The university provides academic advising, career counseling, and health and wellness programs to ensure student well-being and success.</li>
    \n \n<li><b>Commitment to Accessibility:</b> PHINMA UPANG offers scholarships, financial aid, and flexible payment options to support students from diverse backgrounds, ensuring access to quality education.</li>
</string>

    <string name="cite"><b>Bachelor of Science in Information Technology</b></string>
    <string name="cite1">
    <li>The BS in Information Technology program equips students with skills in emerging high-growth areas like cloud computing, data science, AI, and IoT, guided by industry experts.</li>
</string>

    <string name="computereng"><b>Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering</b></string>
    <string name="computereng1">
    <li>The BS in Computer Engineering program prepares students for the field through a curriculum that combines theory and hands-on experience in digital systems, computer architecture, programming, and electronics.</li>
</string>

    <string name="tourism"><b>Bachelor of Science in Tourism Management</b></string>
    <string name="tourism1">
    <li>The BS in Tourism Management program trains students in front office, events planning, cruise line operations, and travel and tours, emphasizing cultural diversity, communication skills, and heritage appreciation. The program offers local and international certifications for employment opportunities.</li>
</string>

</resources>