<resources>
    <string name="app_name">management-app</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="gender_array">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- School items -->
    <string-array name="school_array">
        <item>PHINMA</item>
        <item>UPANG</item>
        <item>MISYUBIBI</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="rad_learning_description">RAD<u> (Reinforced Adaptive Development) </u>Learning at <u>PHINMA University of Pangasinan </u>(UPANG) is an innovative approach to education designed to adapt to the unique needs and circumstances of each student. This system combines traditional classroom learning with advanced technological tools and methodologies to create a flexible, student-centered educational experience.</string>
    <string name="rad1"><u>Blended Learning:</u> RAD integrates face-to-face instruction with online learning, offering students the flexibility to access course materials, participate in discussions, and complete assignments at their own pace.</string>
    <string name="rad2"><u>Personalized Learning Paths:</u> Each students learning journey is tailored to their individual strengths, weaknesses, and learning styles. Adaptive learning technologies analyze student performance and provide customized feedback and resources.</string>
    <string name="rad3"><u>Continuous Assessment:</u> RAD emphasizes ongoing assessment rather than traditional high-stakes exams. This allows for regular feedback and adjustments to the learning process, ensuring students stay on track and master the material.</string>
    <string name="rad4"><u>Collaborative Environment:</u> Students engage in group projects and peer-to-peer learning, fostering a collaborative and supportive community. This approach helps develop critical soft skills such as teamwork, communication, and problem-solving.</string>
    <string name="rad5"><u>Industry-Linked Curriculum:</u> The curriculum is designed in collaboration with industry partners to ensure that it meets the current demands of the job market. This ensures that graduates are job-ready and possess the skills that employers are looking for.</string>
    <string name="rad6"><u>Support Systems:</u> RAD Learning provides comprehensive support through academic advising, tutoring, and mental health services. This holistic approach ensures that students have the resources they need to succeed both academically and personally.</string>
    <string name="rad7"><u>Technology Integration:</u> The use of cutting-edge educational technologies, including learning management systems, virtual labs, and interactive multimedia content, enhances the learning experience and keeps students engaged.</string>

    <string name="flex_learning_description">FLEX<u> (Flexible Learning Experience) </u>at <u>PHINMA University of Pangasinan (UPANG) </u>is an educational model designed to provide students with a versatile and adaptive learning environment that caters to their individual needs and lifestyles. This approach combines various learning modalities to ensure that education is accessible, engaging, and effective for all students.</string>
    <string name="flex1"><u>Hybrid Learning:</u> FLEX incorporates a blend of traditional classroom instruction and online learning. This hybrid model allows students to participate in both in-person and virtual classes, offering the flexibility to balance their studies with other commitments.</string>
    <string name="flex2"><u>Self-Paced Learning:</u> Students have the option to progress through course materials at their own pace. This self-directed approach empowers learners to take control of their education, advancing quickly through familiar topics while spending more time on challenging concepts.</string>
    <string name="flex3"><u>Interactive Online Platforms:</u> FLEX utilizes advanced learning management systems (LMS) and interactive online platforms that provide access to lectures, assignments, quizzes, and discussion forums. These tools enhance the learning experience by making it more interactive and engaging.</string>
    <string name="flex4"><u>Customized Learning Paths:</u> Each students learning journey is tailored to their individual needs and goals. Adaptive learning technologies analyze student performance and preferences, providing personalized recommendations and resources to support their academic growth.</string>
    <string name="flex5"><u>Collaborative Projects:</u> Students participate in collaborative projects and group activities, fostering a sense of community and enhancing teamwork skills. These projects often involve real-world applications, preparing students for professional environments.</string>
    <string name="flex6"><u>Accessibility and Inclusivity:</u> FLEX is designed to be accessible to all students, regardless of their location or circumstances. Online resources and flexible scheduling options ensure that education is available to those who may face geographical, financial, or time constraints.</string>
    <string name="flex7"><u>Comprehensive Support:</u> FLEX Learning offers a range of support services, including academic advising, tutoring, and counseling. These resources help students navigate their educational journey, overcome challenges, and achieve their goals.</string>
    <string name="flex8"><u>Industry-Relevant Curriculum:</u> The curriculum is developed in collaboration with industry experts to ensure that it is relevant to current job market demands. This focus on practical, real-world skills helps students become job-ready upon graduation.</string>
    <string name="flex9"><u>Continuous Assessment and Feedback:</u> FLEX emphasizes continuous assessment through regular quizzes, assignments, and feedback. This approach allows students to monitor their progress and make necessary adjustments to their learning strategies.</string>

    <string name="facetoface_learning_description"><u>Face-to-Face</u> learning at<u> PHINMA University of Pangasinan </u>(UPANG) is the traditional, in-person approach to education, where students and instructors interact directly within the classroom environment. This method emphasizes personal engagement, immediate feedback, and a structured learning experience, fostering a vibrant academic community.</string>
    <string name="facetoface1"><u>Direct Interaction:</u> Students benefit from real-time, face-to-face interactions with instructors and peers. This direct engagement facilitates immediate clarification of doubts, dynamic discussions, and personalized feedback.</string>
    <string name="facetoface2"><u>Structured Environment:</u> The physical classroom provides a structured setting that supports discipline and focus. Scheduled classes and a fixed timetable help students manage their time effectively and maintain a consistent study routine.</string>
    <string name="facetoface3"><u>Hands-On Learning:</u> Face-to-Face learning at PHINMA UPANG emphasizes experiential learning through lab sessions, workshops, and practical exercises. This hands-on approach is particularly beneficial for courses requiring physical demonstration and practice.</string>
    <string name="facetoface4"><u>Community Building:</u> In-person classes foster a sense of community and camaraderie among students. Social interactions, group projects, and extracurricular activities build strong relationships and enhance collaborative skills.</string>
    <string name="facetoface5"><u>Immediate Feedback:</u> Instructors can provide instant feedback and support during class. This immediate response helps students correct mistakes, understand concepts better, and stay engaged with the material.</string>
    <string name="facetoface6"><u>Enhanced Communication Skills:</u> Face-to-Face learning develops essential communication skills. Students practice public speaking, active listening, and interpersonal communication, which are crucial for personal and professional success.</string>
    <string name="facetoface7"><u>Resource Accessibility:</u> On-campus resources, including libraries, labs, and study spaces, are readily available to students. Access to these facilities supports research, experimentation, and group study sessions.</string>
    <string name="facetoface8"><u>Extracurricular Opportunities:</u> Students can participate in various on-campus activities, clubs, and organizations. These opportunities enrich the university experience, promoting personal growth and leadership development.</string>
    <string name="facetoface9"><u>Cultural and Social Exposure:</u> In-person learning exposes students to diverse perspectives and cultures through direct interaction with classmates and faculty. This exposure broadens their understanding and appreciation of different viewpoints.</string>
    <string name="facetoface10"><u>Health and Safety Measures:</u> PHINMA UPANG ensures a safe learning environment by implementing health and safety protocols. These measures include regular sanitation, social distancing, and health monitoring to protect the well-being of students and staff.</string>
</resources>