<resources>
    <string name="app_name">management-app</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="gender_array">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- School items -->
    <string-array name="school_array">
        <item>PHINMA URDANETACITY</item>
        <item>UPANG DAGUPAN</item>
        <item>MISYUBIBI</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="details"><u>Click hereto see details.</u></string>

    <string name="aerial_view"><b>AERIAL VIEW</b></string>
    <string name="street_view"><b>STREET VIEW</b></string>

    <string name="flex_learning"><b><big>FLEX LEARNING</big></b>
        \n <li>Both Distance Learning + Face-to-Face Sessions</li>
        \n <li>Teacher support will be provided via calls, texts, or social media</li>
        \n <li>6-8 subjects in 1 semester</li>
    </string>

    <string name="rad_learning"><b><big>RAD LEARNING</big></b>
        \n <li>Largely Home-based with virtual coaching</li>
        \n <li>For students who cannot come to school</li>
        \n <li>Suited for working students who need flexible learning setup</li>
        \n <li>2 subjects in 1 moth</li>
    </string>

    <string name="calendar"><u>Calendar Event</u></string>
    <string name="handbook"><u>Hand Book</u></string>


    <string name="registrar">
        How to Find the Registrar’s Office:
        \n\n Starting Point: Main Entrance / Ground Floor

        \n \n 1. Enter the school through the main entrance.
        \n 2. Proceed to the central staircase or elevator.
        \n 3. Go to the Second Floor

        \n 4.Take the stairs
        \n 5. Locating the Registrar’s Office

        \n 6. Upon reaching the second floor, look for signage pointing towards the Finance Office and CSDL (Center for Student Development and Leadership).
        \n 7. Walk in the direction of the Finance and CSDL offices.
        \n 8. Registrar’s Office Location

        \n 9. The Registrar’s Office is located right beside the Finance Office and across from CSDL.
    </string>

    <string name="csdl">

        Instructions to Reach the CSDL Second Floor Beside the Registrars Office:
        \n\n <b>1. Start at the Main Entrance:</b>
        \n <li>Enter through the main entrance of the school. If youre starting from a different location, make your way to the main hallway near the Registrars Office.</li>

        \n <b>2. Locate the Registrars Office:</b>
        \n <li>Look for signs or ask nearby staff to confirm the office location.</li>

        \n <b>3. Find the Nearby Staircase:</b>
        \n <li>Next to the Registrar’s Office, there should be a staircase or elevator. Use this to go up to the second floor.</li>

        \n <b>4. Proceed to the CSDL Area:</b>
        \n <li>Upon reaching the second floor, turn in the direction of the CSDL department.</li>

    </string>

    <string name="clinic">

        <b>
            How to Find the CLINIC:
            \n\n 1. Start at the main entrance of the school.
        \n 2. Walk straight down the hallway and find the staircase or elevator that leads to the second floor.
        \n 3. Take the stairs or elevator to the second floor.
        \n 4. When you reach the second floor, walk straight and look for the Female Comfort Room.
        \n 5. The clinic is directly beside the Female Comfort Room on the right-hand side.
        </b>
        <li> \n You should see a sign for the clinic above the door.</li>

    </string>


    <string name="collegedept">

        <b>
            How to Find the College Department and Senior High School Department:
            \n\n 1. Enter the school building through the main entrance.
        \n 2. Proceed straight to ground floor.
        \n 3. Locate the staircase to access the upper floors.
        \n 4. Take thestairs to the 4th floor.
        \n 5. Upon exiting thestairs, walk straight down the hallway.
        \n 6. You will see two doors side by side.
        </b>
        <li>
                \n The door on the left is the College Department.
                \n The door on the right is the Senior High School Department.
            </li>
    </string>

    <string name="library">

        <b>
            How to Find the Library:
            \n\n 1. Enter the school building through the main entrance.
        \n 2. Head straight to ground floor.
        \n 3. Locate the staircase on the right side of the lobby.
        \n 4. Begin ascending the stairs to the upper floors:
        </b>
        <li>
            \n Go up to the 2nd floor.
            \n Continue to the 3rd floor.
            \n Ascend to the 4th floor.
            \n Finally, climb to the 5th floor.
        </li>
        <b>
            \n 5. When you reach the 5th floor, turn left
            \n 6. The library entrance clearly marked with a sign.
        </b>
    </string>


    <string name="secondfloormap">
        <b>SECOND FLOOR MAP</b>
    </string>

    <string name="haha">
        <b>
            How to Find the Mens Comfort room:
            \n\n Enter the school building through the main entrance.
        \n \n 1. Once inside, immediately turn left.
        \n 2. Walk down the hallway until you see a staircase on the left.
        \n 3. Turn left again after passing the staircase.
        \n 4. The mens comfort room will be straight ahead or clearly marked on this side of the building.
        </b>
    </string>

    <string name="lingapwika">LINGAPWIKA COMMUNITY OUTREACH \nPROGRAM - LOCAL SCHOOL</string>
    <string name="eucharistic">EUCHARISTIC CELEBRATION \n- UPANG U Atrium</string>
    <string name="seminar">SEMINAR FOR THE DSPC \nPARTICIPANTS - UPANG U Atrium</string>
    <string name="ningning">NINGNING PROJECT \n- AROUND URDANETA</string>

    <string name="studenthandbook">
        <b>Mission and Vision</b>
        \n \n <b>Mission of the PHINMA Education Network</b>
        \n Through the application of effective management in institutions of higher and basic learning, to give Filipinos better access to affordable high quality education in key cities throughout the Philippines, preparing them to be globally competitive.

        \n \n <b>School Mission</b>
        \n To Develop the Filipino youth into employable global professionals thru the endowment of knowledge and skills and the formation of character and spirit.

        \n \n <b>School Vision</b>
        \n With distinct advantage in English Communication and Information Technology, to be the leading institution of higher learning in the region in the development of globally competitive.
    </string>















    <string name="rad_learning_description">RAD<b> (Reinforced Adaptive Development) </b>Learning at <b>PHINMA University of Pangasinan </b>(UPANG) is an innovative approach to education designed to adapt to the unique needs and circumstances of each student. This system combines traditional classroom learning with advanced technological tools and methodologies to create a flexible, student-centered educational experience.</string>
    <string name="rad1"><b>Blended Learning:</b> RAD integrates face-to-face instruction with online learning, offering students the flexibility to access course materials, participate in discussions, and complete assignments at their own pace.</string>
    <string name="rad2"><b>Personalized Learning Paths:</b> Each students learning journey is tailored to their individual strengths, weaknesses, and learning styles. Adaptive learning technologies analyze student performance and provide customized feedback and resources.</string>
    <string name="rad3"><b>Continuous Assessment:</b> RAD emphasizes ongoing assessment rather than traditional high-stakes exams. This allows for regular feedback and adjustments to the learning process, ensuring students stay on track and master the material.</string>
    <string name="rad4"><b>Collaborative Environment:</b> Students engage in group projects and peer-to-peer learning, fostering a collaborative and supportive community. This approach helps develop critical soft skills such as teamwork, communication, and problem-solving.</string>
    <string name="rad5"><b>Industry-Linked Curriculum:</b> The curriculum is designed in collaboration with industry partners to ensure that it meets the current demands of the job market. This ensures that graduates are job-ready and possess the skills that employers are looking for.</string>
    <string name="rad6"><b>Support Systems:</b> RAD Learning provides comprehensive support through academic advising, tutoring, and mental health services. This holistic approach ensures that students have the resources they need to succeed both academically and personally.</string>
    <string name="rad7"><b>Technology Integration:</b> The use of cutting-edge educational technologies, including learning management systems, virtual labs, and interactive multimedia content, enhances the learning experience and keeps students engaged.</string>

    <string name="flex_learning_description">FLEX<b> (Flexible Learning Experience) </b>at <b>PHINMA University of Pangasinan (UPANG) </b>is an educational model designed to provide students with a versatile and adaptive learning environment that caters to their individual needs and lifestyles. This approach combines various learning modalities to ensure that education is accessible, engaging, and effective for all students.</string>
    <string name="flex1"><b>Hybrid Learning:</b> FLEX incorporates a blend of traditional classroom instruction and online learning. This hybrid model allows students to participate in both in-person and virtual classes, offering the flexibility to balance their studies with other commitments.</string>
    <string name="flex2"><b>Self-Paced Learning:</b> Students have the option to progress through course materials at their own pace. This self-directed approach empowers learners to take control of their education, advancing quickly through familiar topics while spending more time on challenging concepts.</string>
    <string name="flex3"><b>Interactive Online Platforms:</b> FLEX utilizes advanced learning management systems (LMS) and interactive online platforms that provide access to lectures, assignments, quizzes, and discussion forums. These tools enhance the learning experience by making it more interactive and engaging.</string>
    <string name="flex4"><b>Customized Learning Paths:</b> Each students learning journey is tailored to their individual needs and goals. Adaptive learning technologies analyze student performance and preferences, providing personalized recommendations and resources to support their academic growth.</string>
    <string name="flex5"><b>Collaborative Projects:</b> Students participate in collaborative projects and group activities, fostering a sense of community and enhancing teamwork skills. These projects often involve real-world applications, preparing students for professional environments.</string>
    <string name="flex6"><b>Accessibility and Inclusivity:</b> FLEX is designed to be accessible to all students, regardless of their location or circumstances. Online resources and flexible scheduling options ensure that education is available to those who may face geographical, financial, or time constraints.</string>
    <string name="flex7"><b>Comprehensive Support:</b> FLEX Learning offers a range of support services, including academic advising, tutoring, and counseling. These resources help students navigate their educational journey, overcome challenges, and achieve their goals.</string>
    <string name="flex8"><b>Industry-Relevant Curriculum:</b> The curriculum is developed in collaboration with industry experts to ensure that it is relevant to current job market demands. This focus on practical, real-world skills helps students become job-ready upon graduation.</string>
    <string name="flex9"><b>Continuous Assessment and Feedback:</b> FLEX emphasizes continuous assessment through regular quizzes, assignments, and feedback. This approach allows students to monitor their progress and make necessary adjustments to their learning strategies.</string>

    <string name="facetoface_learning_description"><b>Face-to-Face</b> learning at<b> PHINMA University of Pangasinan </b>(UPANG) is the traditional, in-person approach to education, where students and instructors interact directly within the classroom environment. This method emphasizes personal engagement, immediate feedback, and a structured learning experience, fostering a vibrant academic community.</string>
    <string name="facetoface1"><b>Direct Interaction:</b> Students benefit from real-time, face-to-face interactions with instructors and peers. This direct engagement facilitates immediate clarification of doubts, dynamic discussions, and personalized feedback.</string>
    <string name="facetoface2"><b>Structured Environment:</b> The physical classroom provides a structured setting that supports discipline and focus. Scheduled classes and a fixed timetable help students manage their time effectively and maintain a consistent study routine.</string>
    <string name="facetoface3"><b>Hands-On Learning:</b> Face-to-Face learning at PHINMA UPANG emphasizes experiential learning through lab sessions, workshops, and practical exercises. This hands-on approach is particularly beneficial for courses requiring physical demonstration and practice.</string>
    <string name="facetoface4"><b>Community Building:</b> In-person classes foster a sense of community and camaraderie among students. Social interactions, group projects, and extracurricular activities build strong relationships and enhance collaborative skills.</string>
    <string name="facetoface5"><b>Immediate Feedback:</b> Instructors can provide instant feedback and support during class. This immediate response helps students correct mistakes, understand concepts better, and stay engaged with the material.</string>
    <string name="facetoface6"><b>Enhanced Communication Skills:</b> Face-to-Face learning develops essential communication skills. Students practice public speaking, active listening, and interpersonal communication, which are crucial for personal and professional success.</string>
    <string name="facetoface7"><b>Resource Accessibility:</b> On-campus resources, including libraries, labs, and study spaces, are readily available to students. Access to these facilities supports research, experimentation, and group study sessions.</string>
    <string name="facetoface8"><b>Extracurricular Opportunities:</b> Students can participate in various on-campus activities, clubs, and organizations. These opportunities enrich the university experience, promoting personal growth and leadership development.</string>
    <string name="facetoface9"><b>Cultural and Social Exposure:</b> In-person learning exposes students to diverse perspectives and cultures through direct interaction with classmates and faculty. This exposure broadens their understanding and appreciation of different viewpoints.</string>
    <string name="facetoface10"><b>Health and Safety Measures:</b> PHINMA UPANG ensures a safe learning environment by implementing health and safety protocols. These measures include regular sanitation, social distancing, and health monitoring to protect the well-being of students and staff.</string>

    <string name="hka_description"><b>The 25% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG) </b>is a financial aid program designed to assist deserving students in pursuing higher education. This scholarship aims to alleviate the financial burden on students and their families by providing a 25% reduction in tuition fees. PHINMA UPANG is committed to making quality education accessible to more students, and the HK Scholarship is one of the initiatives to support this mission.</string>
    <string name="hka9"><b>Benefits of the 25% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship</b></string>
    <string name="hka1"><b>Reduced Financial Burden:</b> With a 25% discount on tuition fees, the scholarship significantly reduces the overall cost of education, making it more affordable for students and their families.</string>
    <string name="hka2"><b>Access to Quality Education:</b> The scholarship enables more students to access the high-quality education and facilities offered by PHINMA UPANG, which can enhance their learning experience and future career prospects.</string>
    <string name="hka3"><b>Encouragement of Academic Excellence:</b> By providing financial assistance, the scholarship encourages students to strive for academic excellence without the constant worry of financial constraints.</string>
    <string name="hka4"><b>Increased Opportunities:</b> The reduction in tuition fees allows students to allocate their resources to other educational needs such as books, transportation, and living expenses, thereby providing a more comprehensive educational experience.</string>
    <string name="hka5"><b>Support for Deserving Students:</b>> The HK Scholarship is designed to support students who demonstrate academic potential and financial need, ensuring that deserving students are given the opportunity to succeed.</string>
    <string name="hka6"><b>Community Building:</b> Scholarships like the HK Scholarship foster a sense of community and support within the university, as students who receive financial aid are often more engaged and motivated to give back to their peers and the institution.</string>
    <string name="hka7"><b>Long-Term Benefits:</b> By investing in the education of students, PHINMA UPANG is contributing to the development of skilled professionals who can positively impact their communities and the country’s future.</string>
    <string name="hka8"><b>The 25% HawakKamay (HK) Scholarship is an integral part of PHINMA UPANG’s commitment to making education accessible and affordable, thereby empowering students to achieve their academic and professional goals.</b></string>

    <string name="hkb_description"><b>The 50% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b> is a generous financial aid program designed to support academically promising and financially needy students. This scholarship provides a 50% reduction in tuition fees, significantly easing the financial burden on students and their families. PHINMA UPANG, committed to making quality education accessible to more students, offers the HK Scholarship to help deserving individuals achieve their academic and career aspirations.</string>
    <string name="hkb1"><b>Benefits of the 50% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship</b></string>
    <string name="hkb2"><b>Substantial Financial Relief:</b> By offering a 50% discount on tuition fees, the scholarship substantially reduces the cost of education, making it more affordable for students and their families.</string>
    <string name="hkb3"><b>Enhanced Access to Quality Education:</b> The scholarship allows more students to access the high-quality education, resources, and facilities provided by PHINMA UPANG, improving their overall academic experience and future prospects.</string>
    <string name="hkb4"><b>Promotion of Academic Excellence:</b> Financial support through the HK Scholarship motivates students to maintain high academic standards, fostering a culture of excellence and perseverance.</string>
    <string name="hkb5"><b>Broader Educational Opportunities:</b> The reduced financial burden enables students to allocate funds to other essential needs such as textbooks, transportation, and living expenses, enhancing their educational journey.</string>
    <string name="hkb6"><b>Support for Deserving Students**:</b> The HK Scholarship specifically targets students who exhibit academic potential and financial need, ensuring that those who deserve support receive it.</string>
    <string name="hkb7"><b>Community and Peer Support:</b> Recipients of the scholarship often become more engaged in campus activities, contributing to a supportive and vibrant university community.</string>
    <string name="hkb8"><b>Long-Term Impact:</b> By investing in students education, PHINMA UPANG helps develop skilled professionals who can positively impact their communities and contribute to national development.</string>
    <string name="hkb9"><b>Reduction of Financial Stress:</b> With half of the tuition fee covered, students can focus more on their studies and personal growth rather than worrying about financial constraints.</string>
    <string name="hkb10"><b>Empowerment and Confidence:</b> Receiving such a significant scholarship boosts students confidence and self-esteem, empowering them to pursue their goals with greater determination and resilience.</string>
    <string name="hkb11"><b>The 50% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship is a vital component of PHINMA UPANG’s mission to provide accessible and affordable education, empowering students to reach their full potential and contribute meaningfully to society.</b></string>

    <string name="hkc_description"><b>The 75% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b> is a substantial financial aid program designed to support academically outstanding and financially challenged students. This scholarship provides a 75% reduction in tuition fees, significantly alleviating the financial burden on students and their families. PHINMA UPANG is dedicated to making high-quality education accessible to more students, and the HK Scholarship is a key initiative in achieving this goal.</string>
    <string name="hkc1"><b>Benefits of the 75% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship</b></string>
    <string name="hkc2"><b>Major Financial Relief:</b> With a 75% discount on tuition fees, the scholarship greatly reduces the cost of education, making it much more affordable for students and their families.</string>
    <string name="hkc3"><b>Access to Quality Education:</b> The scholarship allows more students to benefit from the high-quality education, resources, and facilities offered by PHINMA UPANG, enhancing their academic experience and future career opportunities.</string>
    <string name="hkc4"><b>Encouragement of Academic Excellence:</b> Financial support through the HK Scholarship incentivizes students to maintain high academic standards, fostering a culture of excellence and perseverance.</string>
    <string name="hkc5"><b>Broader Educational Opportunities:</b> The significant reduction in tuition fees enables students to allocate funds to other essential needs such as textbooks, transportation, and living expenses, enriching their educational journey.</string>
    <string name="hkc6"><b>Support for Deserving Students:</b> The HK Scholarship specifically targets students who demonstrate academic potential and financial need, ensuring that those who deserve support receive it.</string>
    <string name="hkc7"><b>Community and Peer Support:</b> Scholarship recipients often become more engaged in campus activities, contributing to a supportive and vibrant university community.</string>
    <string name="hkc8"><b>Long-Term Impact:</b> By investing in students education, PHINMA UPANG helps develop skilled professionals who can positively impact their communities and contribute to national development.</string>
    <string name="hkc9"><b>Reduction of Financial Stress:</b> With a large portion of the tuition fee covered, students can focus more on their studies and personal growth rather than worrying about financial constraints.</string>
    <string name="hkc10"><b>Empowerment and Confidence:</b> Receiving such a significant scholarship boosts students confidence and self-esteem, empowering them to pursue their goals with greater determination and resilience.</string>
    <string name="hkc11"><b>Enhanced Career Prospects:</b> Graduates of PHINMA UPANG who benefit from the HK Scholarship are better positioned to excel in their chosen careers, having received a solid educational foundation with less financial strain.</string>
    <string name="hkc12"><b>The 75% Hawak Kamay (HK) Scholarship is a crucial part of PHINMA UPANG’s commitment to providing accessible and affordable education, empowering students to reach their full potential and make meaningful contributions to society.</b></string>

    <string name="hkd_description"><b>The 100% Hawak Kamay (HK) Student Assistant (SA) Scholarship at PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b> is a prestigious financial aid program designed for academically talented and financially disadvantaged students. This scholarship offers a full 100% reduction in tuition fees in exchange for students participating in a student assistantship program. By combining financial aid with practical work experience, the HK SA Scholarship aims to develop well-rounded individuals prepared for both academic and professional success.</string>
    <string name="hkd1"><b>Benefits of the 100% Hawak Kaway (HK) Student Assistant (SA) Scholarship</b></string>
    <string name="hkd2"><b>Complete Financial Coverage:</b> The scholarship covers 100% of tuition fees, completely eliminating the financial burden of education and making it accessible for students from all financial backgrounds.</string>
    <string name="hkd3"><b>Work Experience and Skill Development:</b> As part of the student assistantship program, students gain valuable work experience, developing essential skills such as time management, teamwork, and problem-solving.</string>
    <string name="hkd4"><b>Access to Quality Education:</b> The scholarship allows recipients to benefit from the high-quality education, resources, and facilities provided by PHINMA UPANG, enhancing their learning experience and future career opportunities.</string>
    <string name="hkd5"><b>Encouragement of Academic Excellence:</b> With full financial support, students are motivated to maintain high academic standards and focus on their studies without the distraction of financial concerns.</string>
    <string name="hkd6"><b>Holistic Development:</b> The combination of academic and practical work experience fosters the holistic development of students, preparing them for the challenges of the professional world.</string>
    <string name="hkd7"><b>Support for Deserving Students:</b> The HK SA Scholarship targets students who demonstrate academic potential and financial need, ensuring that those who are most deserving receive the support they need to succeed.</string>
    <string name="hkd8"><b>Community and Peer Engagement:</b> Scholarship recipients often become more involved in campus activities and contribute to a supportive and vibrant university community.</string>
    <string name="hkd9"><b>Long-Term Career Benefits:</b> The work experience gained through the student assistantship program enhances students resumes, making them more competitive in the job market and better prepared for their chosen careers.</string>
    <string name="hkd10"><b>Reduction of Financial Stress:</b> With the full tuition fee covered, students can focus more on their studies and personal growth rather than worrying about financial constraints.</string>
    <string name="hkd11"><b>Empowerment and Confidence:</b> Receiving a full scholarship boosts students confidence and self-esteem, empowering them to pursue their goals with greater determination and resilience.</string>
    <string name="hkd12"><b>Networking Opportunities:</b> Working as a student assistant provides opportunities to build professional networks within the university, which can be beneficial for future career prospects.</string>
    <string name="hkd13"><b>The 100% Hawak Kamay (HK) Student Assistant (SA) Scholarship is an integral part of PHINMA UPANG’s commitment to providing accessible, affordable, and high-quality education. This scholarship not only alleviates financial burdens but also equips students with practical skills and experiences, empowering them to achieve their full potential and make meaningful contributions to society.</b></string>

    <string name="aboutus_description"><b>About PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG)</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus1">PHINMA University of Pangasinan (PHINMA UPANG) is a premier institution of higher learning located in Dagupan City, Pangasinan, Philippines. As part of the PHINMA Education network, PHINMA UPANG is committed to providing quality education that transforms lives and communities. The university offers a wide range of undergraduate and graduate programs designed to equip students with the knowledge, skills, and values needed to succeed in their chosen fields.</string>
    <string name="aboutus2"><b>Mission and Vision</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus3">PHINMA UPANG’s mission is to make lives better through education, aiming to provide accessible and affordable education to students from diverse backgrounds. The university envisions itself as a leader in innovative and transformative education, fostering graduates who are not only academically competent but also socially responsible and globally competitive.</string>
    <string name="aboutus4"><b>Academic Excellence</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus5">PHINMA UPANG is renowned for its academic excellence, offering programs across various disciplines including Business, Engineering, Information Technology, Education, Health Sciences, and the Arts and Sciences. The university employs a learner-centered approach, integrating theoretical knowledge with practical application to ensure students are well-prepared for the demands of the modern workforce.</string>
    <string name="aboutus6"><b>Facilities and Resources</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus7">The university boasts state-of-the-art facilities, including modern classrooms, well-equipped laboratories, a comprehensive library, and specialized centers for research and innovation. These resources provide students with a conducive learning environment that supports both their academic and personal growth.</string>
    <string name="aboutus8"><b>Community Engagement</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus9">PHINMA UPANG places a strong emphasis on community engagement and social responsibility. Through various outreach programs and partnerships with local organizations, the university actively contributes to the development and improvement of its surrounding communities. Students are encouraged to participate in these initiatives, fostering a sense of civic duty and social awareness.</string>
    <string name="aboutus10"><b>Student Life</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus11">At PHINMA UPANG, student life is vibrant and dynamic. The university offers a wide range of extracurricular activities, including clubs, organizations, and sports teams, allowing students to pursue their interests and develop their talents outside the classroom. These activities also promote teamwork, leadership, and holistic development.</string>
    <string name="aboutus12"><b>Support Services</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus13">To ensure the well-being and success of its students, PHINMA UPANG provides comprehensive support services including academic advising, career counseling, and health and wellness programs. The university’s dedicated faculty and staff are committed to guiding students throughout their academic journey and helping them achieve their goals.</string>
    <string name="aboutus14"><b>Commitment to Accessibility</b></string>
    <string name="aboutus15">PHINMA UPANG is dedicated to making quality education accessible to all. The university offers various scholarship programs, financial aid, and flexible payment options to support students from different socio-economic backgrounds. This commitment to accessibility ensures that more students have the opportunity to pursue their educational aspirations.</string>

    <string name="cite"><b>Bachelor of Science in Information Technology</b></string>
    <string name="cite1">The Bachelor of Science in Information Technology program provides students with skills and knowledge needed in relevant emerging high-growth areas in the industry. Through our program, we train students with the development and management of contemporary areas such as cloud computing and applications, analytics and data science, artificial intelligence, and the Internet of Things. We use a curriculum based on inputs and guidance from practicing industry experts.</string>

    <string name="computereng"><b>Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering</b></string>
    <string name="computereng1">The Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering (BS Computer Engineering) program is a dynamic and rigorous course designed to prepare students for the ever-evolving field of computer engineering. Our curriculum combines theoretical foundations with hands-on practical experience, ensuring students acquire a strong understanding of both hardware and software aspects of computing systems. Through courses in digital systems, computer architecture, programming, and electronics, students develop the skills necessary for designing and implementing innovative solutions. The program emphasizes problem-solving, critical thinking, and teamwork, essential for addressing the challenges of the digital age. Graduates are well-equipped for careers in areas such as embedded systems, networking, software development, and hardware design, contributing to advancements in technology and computing.</string>

    <string name="tourism"><b>Bachelor of Science in Tourism Management</b></string>
    <string name="tourism1">The Bachelor of Science in Tourism Management trains students in a diverse set of skills necessary for their future careers. We use the active learning methodology in honing students’ skills in functional areas like Front Office, Events Planning, Cruise Line Operations, and Travel and Tours. We develop their communication skills so they can properly guide guests through destinations and address their needs and concerns. We also teach our students the values of cultural diversity, sensitivity and versatility needed in touring guests from different cultures. Most importantly, we instill within them the value of our heritage and culture, so that they may best represent the country as our ambassadors. Our program provides students the chance to earn local and international certifications and diplomas (TESDA, American Hospitality and Lodging Education Institute, School D’ Hospitality of Singapore) for prestigious local and global employment opportunities.</string>
</resources>